This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Watcher, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will come a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
While Buggy and Mr. Three made their way up to level four
in an attempt to break out of Impel Down,
Luffy, who had been poisoned by Warden Magellan,
was injected with a healing hormone from Ivankov,
which will cure him but rob him of ten years of his life.
Me!
All better!
Let's go!
Luffy back in action!
Eva begins the breakout plan!
You can't be human!
What the heck are you?
Nobody survives Magellan's poison!
This isn't enough!
You can't be human!
What the heck are you?
Nobody survives Magellan's poison!
This is straight up bonkers!
Just twenty hours and he walked out on his own!
It's a miracle!
It has to be!
Miracle?
It's something far greater than just that!
Ah!
Whoa!
He absorbed all those calories!
You can't be human!
What the heck are you?
Nobody survives Magellan's poison!
This is straight up bonkers!
Just twenty hours and he walked out on his own!
It's a miracle!
It has to be!
Miracle?
It's something far greater than just that!
Straw hat!
I'm so happy!
It's Bon!
Glad to see you're alive!
What?
Like I died?
Stop kicking my chain!
You're the one who made me worry!
Straw hat!
Hey, Bon!
What's wrong?
You didn't die just now, did you?
Say something!
Hey!
Bon Boy's all worn out.
Better to let him rest.
Yo, what's up, Eva?
Show some respect!
Thanks, buddy.
That did the trick.
Oh, and thanks for helping out Bon, too.
Well, I do my best.
But I'm not the one you should be thanking.
Bon Boy worked hard for you.
Huh?
Yes, I nudged you along in the right direction.
And yes, my powers are certainly wonderful.
But this one's the hero.
Bon Boy stayed with you all night long.
Struggling and suffering for hours and hours, never relenting.
He lost his voice.
He could barely stand.
He even spewed blood.
But he never stopped.
He shouted, hang in there, and you have to live again and again.
Your recovery was far beyond miraculous.
I can only imagine that it's thanks to all of his efforts.
I see.
Wait a minute.
Is he...
Naked?
Straw Boy, I've come here to rescue you!
In the name of our everlasting friendship!
Who the hell is that?
He's covered in blood.
Before...
I...
I ran away!
Hey, pal.
How do you...
Know him?
He's my friend!
Straw Boy!
I'm not letting you die!
Thank you, Bon.
You're awesome!
I owe you my life!
Thank you, Bon.
You're awesome!
I owe you my life!
I have your clothes, but I'm afraid you're not ready to up and leave just yet.
It will take several days of rest and recuperation before you're back to your old self.
I don't have time for that!
I've already wasted too much!
Sorry to ask, but would you mind looking after Bon for me?
I'll be back for him later!
Be careful!
You see?
Like he said, you've got some healing to do.
Looks like the paper's still pointing down.
Ace is close.
By the way, where am I?
What's that thing?
It's a Vivre card, I believe.
But to answer your question, you're on the floor between level five and six.
I assume now you want to go rescue your brother, regardless of what advice we might give you.
Well, it's your life after all.
You can do whatever you want with it.
Are you gonna make an escape too, Eva?
Before Bon and I got all messed up, he was planning on breaking your butt out of here.
Don't talk about his blast!
If you are gonna leave, can you show me where Ace is on your way out?
Wait, what did you say?
Bon Boy sought out yours truly to help rescue me.
Huh.
Wow.
How charming of him.
And a sweet gesture indeed.
But alas, I have no need to be saved.
It is not my time to break out just yet.
I know what's going on in the world right now.
There's been a shift in the tide and big changes are coming.
The Navy and the Whitebeard Pirates are taking center stage.
Even so, the big man's still waiting things out.
I'm of course referring to my comrade, the leader of all revolutionaries in the world.
You may know him as Dragon!
Oh, you're talking about my dad.
Yes, that's the plan.
When your dad makes a move with that army of his, then I shall do some maneuvering of my own.
Call it my grand comeback tour.
If I were to escape from this place now, I'd just end up on a sea of wanted lists.
Hmm?
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da!
Dad!
Dragon's her dad!
What?
Oh, dear Papa.
And I never knew.
Goodness!
Don't be ridiculous!
Dragon doesn't have any children!
That's just crazy talk!
Ugh.
Maybe I shouldn't have said anything.
Ah, whatever.
Grandpa didn't keep it a secret.
The name of your father is Monkey D. Dragon, the revolutionary.
I don't really know that much about him.
I've never even seen his face before.
What?
But wait, this might be legit.
He doesn't come across as the kind of person who would lie, and he is a rather impressive pirate in his own way.
Plus, the vitality he's shown is the stuff of legends.
An extraordinary father and an extraordinary son.
Please tell me, where did you come from?
Huh?
He's blue.
Sage Dragon.
When you step out for air, you always seem to face in the same direction, no matter where we go.
Do I?
Huh?
I suppose I never gave it much thought.
Bit strange that you would bring it up, isn't it?
Well, I wondered if it was some sort of homing instinct.
You know, the same thing animals have.
Thinking of home, perhaps some family in the east, maybe?
That's enough.
Don't stick your nose in my past.
As you wish.
Hang on.
Oh, no.
If Straw Hat Boy really is Dragon's son, this could be a disaster.
Inazuma!
Check to see when they're taking Ace Boy away.
Yes, of course.
There isn't much time.
The fever card was pointing down, which means he's still here and still alive.
Thank goodness.
Get me that info as soon as possible.
I'm heading to level six with Straw Hat Boy right now.
Yeah?
You're really gonna show me the way?
Hey, wait, you just said level six.
I thought Ace was on five.
Actually, you're already below level five.
Okay, whatever.
All right!
Let's go!
I wasn't paying attention.
It didn't occur to me before.
If Straw Hat Boy is Dragon's son as he claims, then that means so is Ace.
Is this why the Navy captured him and plans his execution?
But that's ludicrous, not to mention suicidal.
There's no way they'd pick a fight with Whitebeard and Dragon at the same time.
What does the world government hope to gain from all this?
In any case, I have no choice but to make my move.
Bon, rest.
I'll be back later, okay?
Straw Hat Boy!
Listen closely.
You need to keep that a secret.
Do not let people know the Dragon's your father.
Yeah, I just figured that out.
I'm his dear friend, as well as one of his trusted commanders.
That means I'm a revolutionary.
That's the reason I was arrested.
So it's my duty to help you, whether you like it or not.
I can't just stand around and let my friend's son die before my eyes.
Listen up!
Tell everyone in the Newcoma Land.
We're going to move fast and rescue Ace Boy before his execution.
And then we'll break out of Impel Down.
Does everyone understand?
No, no, no.
No, no.
Does everyone understand?
Wah!
It's so sudden!
But I don't know if I'm ready.
I don't know if I like this one!
weisen herrew?
A crossroad in life comes without warning.
If you're prepared to fight, then be prepared to die!
Get ready for action and wait for our return!
Alright then, let's do it!
Yay!
I'll follow you wherever you lead!
This is a no-op dancers like aon People of Newcoma Land!
All right! I'm coming to save you, Ace! Now let's go!
His pulse is...
What? What is it? Tell us!
Just fine.
That's not funny!
But the treatment he went through to cure Magellan's poison was harsh and shortened his lifespan.
It's only natural he's still an eensy bit pooped.
Emporio...
Energy hormone!
Yeah!
It's a matter of adrenaline.
I just injected you with enough of it for a full day.
Just to let you know, you're gonna feel the side effects several days from now, but by that point, let's hope it won't really matter.
Oh!
order headpiece thing and yet I feel so empty you know why cuz I haven't earned
it until I've crushed Magellan right good luck with that and let me remind you
if we get tricked or beaten again not only the warden's job but your job will
be on the line my position too yeah of course
surely the staircase to level three is somewhere close by level four is a lot
easier this time just hold on a minute it's a surveillance transponder snail be
careful if it notices us all of our efforts will have been in vain good eyes
partner nice fine we'll just have to be extra sneaky from here on
what is this stuff my eyes are itching like crazy this this must be Magellan's work
the poison he used when he was fighting straw head is still floating around in the air here
oh crap the gods will see us for sure now we're right in this line of sight
that was a close one
you're late sir
you're strict domino try to empty your vows faster next time not possible
not again you'll have to hold it in I can't we need to be at the front gate at 9 a.m. sharp to
officially transfer the prisoner that is the mission placed before us if we don't
make it in time we'll ruin the reputation of impel down
all right listen up our mission is to take custody of port custody ace and then transfer
him to the marine board navy headquarters got it until the moment that we hand over
that prisoner I need each and every one of you on full alert yes sir that we're ready
for any possibility we're moving him in a convoy of five ships under the direction of five vice
sand rules we cannot afford a single slip-up understood sir
I don't know why but I got a crap ton of energy
good you're going to need it we can't afford to waste even a second
there's no security here so flex those leg muscles and run like crazy straw hat boy
nothing can stop us
hey what's going on over there who are those weirdos
uh Ivankov no way I thought he was dead no it can't be
no time for you
death squeak
wheeze
Inazuma open it up
right
they'll be monitoring us from now on
who cares let them come
we have intruders
they're running down the staircase between level five and six
wait the guy with the big head he's that queen of the queers that went missing years ago
name's Ivankov
where's he been hiding we gave up on that guy ages ago
the one running next to him is straw hat luffy
I thought the warden took care of him but he looks as healthy as ever
the third one is another missing prisoner
Inazuma a revolutionary from the south blue
what the hell is going on
looks like they're heading straight for level six
I think they're trying to save fire fizzed ace
domino and warden magellan are also on their way to level six for the transfer as we speak
they're all gonna bump into each other
how can they all still be alive
vice warden when you get here
activate the passageway trapped immediately
call all the jailers on level six
tell them to get ready
they'll need to stand their ground until mistress sadie and the demon guards arrive as reinforcements
report everything that's going on to all floors in warden magellan
you have your orders get movie right yes sir
i've never seen the vice warden so serious before maybe it's the impostor again
we have to stop these troublemakers since i can't blame the warden for this one i mean
oh no he's the real deal
we can make it we can make it
hang on ace i'm coming for you
you
Let's go.
This is it, Quarkus D. Ace.
You're going to be transferred to Marineford.
Upon your arrival there, you will be taken to the execution grounds.
The public execution of Ace is in six hours.
Luffy finally reaches the lowest level of Impel Down, the legendary level six.
Unfortunately, he finds that his brother has already been taken away.
Desperate to catch Ace before he leaves the prison, Luffy makes chase, but is stopped dead in his tracks by Hannibal's trap.
On the next, One Piece, Ace's convoy begins.
Battle on the lowest floor, level six.
I'm going to be king of the pirates.